<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on A minimal Hugo website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on A minimal Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Signals from the gut microbiota to distant organs in physiology and disease</title>
      <link>/nature-medicion/signals-from-the-gut-microbiota-to-distant-organs-in-physiology-and-disease/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nature-medicion/signals-from-the-gut-microbiota-to-distant-organs-in-physiology-and-disease/</guid>
      <description>Signals from the gut microbiota to distant organs in physiology and diseaseGut microbiota convert environmental signals and dietary molecules into signaling metabolites to communicate with the host (Contreras et al., 2016).
ReferenceContreras, A.V., Cocom-Chan, B., Hernandez-Montes, G., Portillo-Bobadilla, T., and Resendis-Antonio, O. (2016). Host-microbiome interaction and cancer: Potential application in precision medicine. Frontiers in Physiology 7, 1–23.
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Note on A blogdown Tutorial</title>
      <link>/note/2017/06/14/another-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/note/2017/06/14/another-note/</guid>
      <description>I just discovered an awesome tutorial on blogdown written by Alison. I have to admit this is the best blogdown tutorial I have seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Quick Note on Two Beautiful Websites</title>
      <link>/note/2017/06/13/a-quick-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/note/2017/06/13/a-quick-note/</guid>
      <description>To me, the two most impressive websites based on blogdown are:
 Rob J Hyndman&amp;rsquo;s personal website. Live Free or Dichotomize by Lucy and Nick et al.  I&amp;rsquo;m sure there will be more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo XMin</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>XMin is the first Hugo theme I have designed. The original reason that I wrote it was I needed a minimal example of Hugo themes when I was writing the blogdown book. Basically I wanted a simple theme that supports a navigation menu, a home page, other single pages, lists of pages, blog posts, categories, tags, and RSS. That is all. Nothing fancy. In terms of CSS and JavaScript, I really want to keep them minimal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>